{
    "subject": "resource/John_Gardner_(British_writer)",
    "predicate": "ontology/notableWork",
    "object": "resource/List_of_James_Bond_novels_and_short_stories",
    "human_readable": "John Gardner (British writer) is notable for 'List of James Bond novels and short stories'.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9068253636360168,
            "question": "Which famous series of novels and short stories did John Gardner write?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7102639675140381,
            "question": "Who is John Gardner?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.669784426689148,
            "question": "What is John Gardner known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6495569944381714,
            "question": "Is John Gardner considered a successful author?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6218746304512024,
            "question": "Name some works by John Gardner."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48078060150146484,
            "question": "Were there any notable adaptations of John Gardner's work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4718255400657654,
            "question": "What is the significance of John Gardner's contributions to literature?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44790127873420715,
            "question": "What genre are the works written by John Gardner typically classified as?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43306809663772583,
            "question": "What nationality is John Gardner?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4105100631713867,
            "question": "What other works besides the James Bond series are attributed to John Gardner?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=John Gardner (British writer) is notable for 'List of James Bond novels and short stories'.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8191_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What nationality is John Gardner?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8191_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre are the works written by John Gardner typically classified as?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8191_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the significance of John Gardner's contributions to literature?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8191_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8191_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8191_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8191_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8191_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8191_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8191_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8191_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8191_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8191_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8191_93.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about John Gardner as a British novelist who wrote extensively, including sixteen books in the James Bond series. This supports the statement that he is notable for contributing to the \"List of James Bond novels and short stories.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}